{"status":"Success","data":{"general_datas":[{"q_number":"407","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30"},{"q_number":"408","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15 \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"409","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"410","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d41\u0d32 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"411","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d1f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"412","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0f\u0d15 \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"413","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d\u200c \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d21\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"414","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"415","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d17\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02"},{"q_number":"416","question":"\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u200c \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"417","question":"\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d57 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"418","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"419","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d35\u0d47\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23 \u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"420","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d47\u0d16\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d\r\n?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48 "},{"q_number":"421","question":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"422","question":"\u0d24\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"423","question":"\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d32\u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"424","question":"\u0d05\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"425","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15"},{"q_number":"426","question":"\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d41\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d17"},{"q_number":"427","question":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"428","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17"},{"q_number":"429","question":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d17"},{"q_number":"430","question":"\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d7b\u0d1c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4a ,\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d40 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"431","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"432","question":"\u0d1f\u0d48\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"433","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"434","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41 \u0d1c\u0d32 \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d15( \u0d12\u0d31\u0d40\u0d38 )"},{"q_number":"435","question":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"436","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d1c\u0d32 \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d46\u0d30\u0d41"},{"q_number":"437","question":"\u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d20\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d12\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d1c\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"438","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30"},{"q_number":"439","question":"\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"440","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02"},{"q_number":"441","question":"\u0d05\u0d7d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"442","question":"\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d42\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"443","question":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"2400 \u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d40"},{"q_number":"444","question":"\u0d05\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d08\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"445","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"446","question":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15"},{"q_number":"447","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d40"},{"q_number":"448","question":"\u0d2e\u0d57\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"449","question":"\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d48\u0d28"},{"q_number":"450","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d35 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d34\u0d41\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"451","question":"\u0d0e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"452","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d16\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d4c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2c\u0d41"},{"q_number":"453","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d02"},{"q_number":"454","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d46\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"455","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"456","question":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7e \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"467","question":"\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17, \u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d28, \u0d38\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"468","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d15\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d41\u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41\r\n"},{"q_number":"469","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"760 \u0d15\u0d3f.\u0d2e\u0d40\r\n"},{"q_number":"470","question":"'\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02' \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"471","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"472","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"473","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d31\u0d40\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d32 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"474","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"475","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d27\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d16\u0d32?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1b\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d20\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"476","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d15\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d3f , \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"477","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"92%\r\n"},{"q_number":"478","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02\r\n","answer":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"479","question":"'\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d32 \u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"480","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n"},{"q_number":"481","question":"\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"482","question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d16\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\r\n"},{"q_number":"483","question":"\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d.?\r\n","answer":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"484","question":"\u0d38\u0d24\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48\r\n"},{"q_number":"485","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"486","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35\r\n"},{"q_number":"487","question":"\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d40\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d02\u0d37\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"488","question":"\u0d21\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"489","question":"\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"490","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d35\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d02\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3e \u0d0e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"491","question":"\u0d18\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"564","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"24 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c 40 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"565","question":"\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d2c\u0d7a \u0d21\u0d48 \u0d13\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d48\u0d21\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"566","question":"\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n","answer":"6779km\r\n"},{"q_number":"567","question":"\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e .....?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 38% \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"568","question":"\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e .....?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d57\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37 \u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 0.7% \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"569","question":"\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32 ?\r\n","answer":"-60\u00b0C\r\n"},{"q_number":"570","question":"\u0d38\u0d57\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d25\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d40\u0d36\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\r\n"},{"q_number":"571","question":"\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"572","question":"\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d39\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d, \u0d21\u0d40\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"573","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n","answer":"22\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f 50 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c\r\n"},{"q_number":"617","question":"\u0d05\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d32\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d13\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"618","question":"\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"8\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d 20 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"619","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d39\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d47\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\r\n"},{"q_number":"620","question":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u200c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d (\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 420\u0d2e\u0d40.\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46)\r\n"},{"q_number":"621","question":"\u0d26\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"647","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d18\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"2011\r\n"},{"q_number":"648","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"649","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"650","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"31%\r\n"},{"q_number":"661","question":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d13\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"662","question":"\u0d2a\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d46\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d17\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"}]},"code":"100"}